Guide to the Jacki Apple Papers MSS.173
Fales Library and Special Collections
Jacki Apple Papers
1976-2012
Fales Library and Special Collections
Apple, Jacki
MSS.173
8.75 Linear Feet in 1 record carton, 12 manuscript boxes, 1 half manuscript box, 4 small flat boxes, and 2 small media boxes
Jacki Apple is a professor at Art Center College of Design in Pasadena, California. Her career has spanned a range of visual and media arts. Her radio show Soundings, of which she was the host and producer, was on KPFK-FM Los Angeles Public Radio from 1981-1995. The Jacki Apple Papers includes correspondence with artists and listeners, promotional material from artists and record labels, memos and letters pertatining to KPFK Los Angeles Public Radio business, cue sheets, and recordings of music, audio art, and interviews that were featured on the show. The collection also includes grant applications, publications, original writings, and audio recordings of proposed and completed artistic endeavors Apple pursued as an individual artist, with collaborators, and through the non-profit Cactus Foundation she was a co-founder of. The projects documented in the collection illustrate the breadth of Apple's artistic output, including public arts commissions, multimedia installations,
Biographical Note
Jacki Apple is a visual, performance and media artist, writer, producer, and a professor at Art Center College of Design in Pasadena, California. Her career has spanned a range of the visual and media arts. She has written, directed, and produced interdisciplinary performance works, worked in costume design, composed and produced soundtracks, created multimedia installations, and worked with mediums of photography, audio, radio, film, site specific works, public art, and beyond.
Raised and educated in New York, Apple relocated to Los Angeles in 1981 where she continued to develop as an artist. An innovator in radio art, she was the host and producer of Soundings, her one hour weekly live radio show on KPFK-FM Los Angeles Public Radio from 1981-1995. Additionally, she co-produced the annual Earjam avant-garde music festival 2000-2004, and was a contributing editor to High Performance magazine. She has written for numerous other art publications, and has taught at both the Art Center College of Design and the University of California, San Diego. In New York City she was a co-founder and first curator of Franklin Furnace 1976-1980. Apple's copious output of solo exhibitions, performance pieces, radio works, and installations have appeared domestically and internationally.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into eleven series as follows:
Series I: KFPK Soundings
Series II: Record Label/Studios
Series III: Press/Promo/Catalogues
Series IV: Soundings- Radio Works/Spoken Word/Sound
Series V: Soundings- Music Tapes
Series VI: Radio Tapes with Jacki Apple/Audio Networks
Series VII: Radio Tapes with Jacki Apple/Soundings
Series VII: Artist Tapes
Series VIII: Soundings Miscellaneous
Series IX: Business Correspondence
Series X. Critical Writing on the Arts
Series XI. Media Works
Series I-VIII are arranged alpahbetically; Series IX-XI have not been arranged by an archivist and appear in the rough alphabetical order in which they were received.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open without restrictions.
Scope and Contents
The Jacki Apple Papers (dated 1976-2012) consist of materials created and collected by Apple documenting her career as an artist, producer, and eductor. The collection includes correspondence with artists and listeners, promotional material from artists and record labels, memos and letters pertatining to KPFK Los Angeles Public Radio buisness, cue sheets, and recordings of music, audio art, and interviews that were featured on the show. Materials in this collection also include grant applications, publications, original writings, and audio recordings of proposed and completed artistic endeavors Apple pursued as an individual artist, with collaborators, and through the non-profit Cactus Foundation she was a co-founder of. The projects documented in the collection illustrate the breadth of Apple's artistic output, including public arts commissions, multimedia installations, interdisciplinary performances, and recorded sound, with her EARJAM music festival and radio art series Redefining Democracy in America particularly well-represented. The collection also documents Apple's career as a critic and theorist through her original, published writings on various aspects of modern art and performance art in the late 20th century.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The Jacki Apple Papers were donated by Jacki Apple in 2005 and 2017. The accession numbers associated with these gifts are 2005.173 and 2018.075.
Audiovisual Access Policies and Procedures
Audiovisual materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers. Materials not yet digitized will need to have access copies made before they can be used. To request an access copy, or if you are unsure if an item has been digitized, please contact fales.library@nyu.edu with the collection name, collection number, and a description of the item(s) requested. A staff member will respond to you with further information.
Press kits.; Personal correspondence.; Poetry reading; Avant-garde (Music); Interviews.; Press releases.; Promotional materials; Audiotapes.; Sound recordings.; Los Angeles (Calif.); Audiocassettes.; Performance art.; Performance artists.; Women performance artists; Performance art -- History and criticism; Arts, Modern -- 20th century; Anderson, Laurie, 1947-; Burroughs, William S., 1914-1997; Sondheim, Alan; Gray, Spalding, 1941-2004; Russell, Arthur
- Series I: KPFK Soundings, 211281
  - Artist Correspondence, 1987, 1989, 1990-1995, Undated; cuid20936; 211284 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Artist Letters and Distribution Letters, 1981-1983, 1985-1988; cuid20937; 211282 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence/Business, 1979, 1986-1989, 1992-1995; cuid20938; 211287 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - KPFK Cue Sheets 1 of 3, 1989-1995, Undated; cuid20939; 211290 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - KPFK Cue Sheets 2 of 3, 1985-1989, Undated; cuid20940; 211291 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - KPFK Cue Sheets 3 of 3, 1981-1984, Undated; cuid20941; 211292 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Listener Letters, 1986-1987, 1989, 1991-1994, Undated; cuid20942; 211293 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Promo Sheets/PR/Bios, 1986-1987, Undated; cuid20943; 211294 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Series II: Record Labels/Studios, 211283
  - Cuneiform Records (USA)/Rer Recommended (London), 1991, 1996-1999; cuid20944; 211296 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Experimental Sound Studios/Lou Mallozi, 1987-1991, 1997, Undated; cuid20945; 211297 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Lipp Service, 1994-1997; cuid20946; 211298 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - No Problem, 1994-1997, Undated; cuid20947; 211299 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Series III: Press/Promo/Catalogues, 211295
  - Catalogues-Distribution CDs/Records/Tapes, 1990, 1992-1997, 1999, Undated; cuid20948; 211300 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, 1994-1996, Undated; cuid20949; 211301 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Johnny Coleman, 1994; cuid20950; 211302 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Lynn Book Press Kit, 1992-1994; cuid20951; 211305 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Misc- Press/Flyers/PR/Bios 1 of 2, 1987-1989, 1991-1992, 1993-1995, 1997-1998; cuid20952; 211306 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Misc- Press/Flyers/PR/Bios 2 of 2, 1989, 1993-1997; cuid20953; 211307 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Press Kits, 1989, 1990, 1993, 1994; cuid20954; 211308 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Press Releases/Promotional Material, 1991-1996, 2000, Undated; cuid20955; 211313 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Press Releases/Promotional Material, 1992-1996, 1999, Undated; cuid20956; 211314 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Reviews, 1990, 1991, 1994, Undated; cuid20957; 211315 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Series IV: Sound recordings - Radio Works/Spoken Word/Sound, 1985-1995; 211316
  - Subseries A: Access Copies, cuid20958; 211317
    Conditions Governing Access
    Sound recordings have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers.
  - Subseries B: Originals, 211318
    - Mix Parade Vol.1 - Tom Skelly, 1987-1988; ID; 173.0001; 211319 (Box 2, Media ID; 173.0001)
      Currently unavailable until duplication occurs.
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
      Original format: 1/4" audiocassette
    - Mix Parade - Tom Skelly/Frank Ridenour, 1987-1988; ID: 173.0002; 211320 (Box 2, Media ID: 173.0002)
    - Mix Parade #2 - Tom Skelly/Frank Ridenour, 1987-1988; ID: 173.0003; 211322 (Box 2, Media ID: 173.0003)
    - This Is America - Terra Infirma, 1988; ID: 173.0004; 211323 (Box 2, Media ID: 173.0004)
    - The Campaign Game - E Productions 1. The Campaign Game 2. Situation Room, undated; ID: 173.0005; 211324 (Box 2, Media ID: 173.0005)
    - RadioArcade - E Productions 1. Episode III- The American Dream 2. Episode IV - The Deep End, 1986; ID: 173.006; 211326 (Box 2, Media ID: 173.006)
    - War, Peace & Poetry: Guatemala - Weaving Rainbows From Black Sacks of Silence- Andrew Leslie Phillips, 1989; ID: 173.0007; 211327 (Box 2, Media ID: 173.0007)
    - Untitled #1 Essex Hemphill & Wayson Jones, undated; ID: 173.0008; 211346 (Box 2, Media ID: 173.0008)
    - Untitled #2 Essex Hemphill & Wayson Jones, undated; ID: 173.0009; 211347 (Box 2, Media ID: 173.0009)
    - Sound Pieces - Patsy Rahn, undated; ID: 173.0010; 211349 (Box 2, Media ID: 173.0010)
    - Speak To Me - Paul Voudouris, undated; ID: 173.0011; 211352 (Box 2, Media ID: 173.0011)
    - Untitled - Arleen Sclhoss, 1984; ID: 173.0012; 211354 (Box 2, Media ID: 173.0012)
    - Power of The Dreamer - Jimmy Townes/Trance Band, 1985; ID: 173.0013; 211356 (Box 2, Media ID: 173.0013)
    - It's All in the Wrist - Lisa Kucharski, 1995; ID: 173.001; 211360 (Box 2, Media ID: 173.001)
    - Kir Madiannand & Other Plays - Alison Lune, 1994-1995; ID: 173.0075; 211361 (Box 2, Media ID: 173.0075)
    - A Change of Heart - Nicholas Smith, undated; ID: 173.0016; 211362 (Box 2, Media ID: 173.0016)
    - Pressing the Flesh - The Manic Kingdom, 1992; ID: 173.0017; 211369 (Box 2, Media ID: 173.0017)
    - Sounds Familiar - Neville, Crotty & Sparling, undated; ID: 173.0018; 211371 (Box 2, Media ID: 173.0018)
      Related Materials
- Series V: Audio: Soundings- Music Tapes, 1985-1995; 211614
  - Subseries A: Access Copies, cuid20959; 211615
  - Subseries B: Originals, 211617
    - Damaged - Alan Sondheim, 1986; ID: 173.0019; 211618 (Box 2, Media ID: 173.0019)
    - Damaged #2- (A). Square Dance the Rich (B) 1.Dallas Concert Live 2.Cricket 8/86 With Cricket - Alan Sondheim, undated; February 3,1986; August 1986; ID: 173.0020; 211623 (Box 2, Media ID: 173.0020)
    - Rotated Guitar - Mark Wheaton, 1987; ID: 173.0021; 211625 (Box 2, Media ID: 173.0021)
    - de/signer- For String Quartet - David Dramm, 1988; ID: 173.0022; 211628 (Box 2, Media ID: 173.0022)
    - by - For Two Flutes - David Dramm, 1987; ID: 173.0023; 211630 (Box 2, Media ID: 173.0023)
    - Temple of Collage - Michael Avery Bell, 1989; ID: 173.002; 211633 (Box 3, Media ID: 173.002)
    - Being There - Michael Avery Bell, 1989; ID: 173.0025; 211634 (Box 2, Media ID: 173.0025)
    - Untitled- Non Credo, 1987; ID: 173.0026; 211635 (Box 2, Media ID: 173.0026)
    - Siren Song- Nigel Helyer, 1992; ID: 173.0027; 211636 (Box 2, Media ID: 173.0027)
    - Technical Tape - Science, 1986; ID: 173.0028; 211637 (Box 2, Media ID: 173.0028)
    - Breaded- Steaming Coils/Brad Laner, 1989; ID: 173.0029; 211638 (Box 2, Media ID: 173.0029)
    - Limpopo (Self-titled), 1991; ID: 173.0030; 211639 (Box 2, Media ID: 173.0030)
    - Omaggio a Futi - Motor Totemist Guild, 1988; ID: 173.0031; 211640 (Box 2, Media ID: 173.0031)
    - Untitled - Hisaso Shinagawa, 1992; ID: 173.0032; 211641 (Box 2, Media ID: 173.0032)
    - Untitled - Tom Guralnick/David Moss, 1988; ID: 173.0033; 211642 (Box 2, Media ID: 173.0033)
    - Sonistruction - Tom Guralnick, 1988; ID: 173.0034; 211643 (Box 2, Media ID: 173.0034)
    - The Other Woman - Jill Fido, 1992; ID: 173.0035; 211644 (Box 2, Media ID: 173.0035)
    - Music From Performances - Yura Adams, undated; ID: 173.0036; 211645 (Box 2, Media ID: 173.0036)
    - Red Bird - Trevor Wishart, undated; ID: 173.0037; 211647 (Box 2, Media ID: 173.0037)
    - Suburban Bird Calls - D. Scott Hessels, undated; ID: 173.0038; 211648 (Box 2, Media ID: 173.0038)
    - CNLF Radio Sampler, undated; ID: 173.0039; 211649 (Box 2, Media ID: 173.0039)
    - Mindsight - Steve Nelson Rainey, undated; ID: 173.0040; 211650 (Box 2, Media ID: 173.0040)
    - The Blue Night/Lives of Saints - Fredrick Moore, undated; ID: 173.0041; 211651 (Box 2, Media ID: 173.0041)
    - While All Slept - YSC, 1993; ID: 173.0042; 211652 (Box 2, Media ID: 173.0042)
    - The Voices of Kwahn - Max Bilt, 1993; ID: 173.0043; 211653 (Box 2, Media ID: 173.0043)
    - Once Despised: Thine Eyes, undated; ID: 173.0044; 211654 (Box 2, Media ID: 173.0044)
    - Living Inside Design - Mikel Rouse, undated; ID: 173.0045; 211655 (Box 2, Media ID: 173.0045)
    - Smut - Dave Soldier, undated; ID: 173.0046; 211656 (Box 2, Media ID: 173.0046)
    - Talking Drum - Chris Brown, 1995; ID: 173.0047; 211657 (Box 2, Media ID: 173.0047)
    - Private Boundaries- Silent Tongues, 1992; ID: 173.0048; 211658 (Box 2, Media ID: 173.0048)
    - Let the Dead Bury the Living - Steve Gibson, 1993; ID: 173.0049; 211659 (Box 2, Media ID: 173.0049)
    - Feed Ink #1 - green - Audio Magazine from gamma Knife- Errant Bodies Productions, undated; ID: 173.0050; 211660 (Box 2, Media ID: 173.0050)
    - Feed Ink #2- silver- Audio Magazine from gamma KNife- Errant Bodies Productions, undated; ID: 173.0051; 211661 (Box 2, Media ID: 173.0051)
    - Feed Ink #3 - gold - Audio Magazine from Gamma Knife - Errant Bodies Productions, undated; ID: 173.0052; 211662 (Box 2, Media ID: 173.0052)
- Series VI: Audio: Radio Tapes with Jacki Apple/Audio Networks, 1982-1985; 211663
  Scope and Content
  Interviews & Live Performances with Jacki Apple
  - Subseries A: Access Copies, cuid20960; 211664
  - Subseries B: Originals, 211665
    - A. Audio Networks Zone 23 - Rosenthal B. Rosenthal Interview -- Rachel Rosenthal, 1982; ID: 173.0053; 211667 (Box 3, Media ID: 173.0053)
    - A. Audio Networks:Zone 23 Burroughs/Anderson B. Gierno/Kroser -- William Burroughs, Laurie Anderson, 1982; ID: 173.0054; 211668 (Box 3, Media ID: 173.0054)
    - A. Jill Kroesen - Audio Networks: Zone 23 (1 of 2), 1982; ID: 173.0055; 211671 (Box 3, Media ID: 173.0055)
    - A. Jill Kroesen - Audio Networks: Zone 23 (2 of 2), 1982; ID: 173.0056; 211672 (Box 3, Media ID: 173.0056)
    - A. Jacki Apple, Robert Raposo, Bruce Tovsky Talk for One Hour, 1982; ID: 173.0057; 211675 (Box 3, Media ID: 173.0057)
    - A. Audio Networks - Garrett List A-1 Band "Fire & Ice", 1982; ID: 173.006; 211676 (Box 3, Media ID: 173.006)
    - A. Audio Networks Zone 23 - KPFK Los Angeles - Henry Korn, 1982; ID: 173.0059; 211677 (Box 3, Media ID: 173.0059)
    - A. Gina Wendkos Interview, 1985; ID: 173.0060; 211678 (Box 3, Media ID: 173.0060)
    - A. Harold Budd- KFPK Auido Networks B. New Music America Artists, October 14, 1985; undated; ID: 173.0061; 211680 (Box 3, Media ID: 173.0061)
    - A. Interview- Lee Breuer, Bob Telson, Jacki Apple, 1985; ID: 173.0062; 211681 (Box 3, Media ID: 173.0062)
    - Notes: On Performance - Tony Abatemarco, Jan Munroe, David Schweizer, Susan Falcon, 1985; ID: 173.0063; 211682 (Box 3, Media ID: 173.0063)
- Series VII: Audio: Radio Tapes with Jacki Apple/Soundings, 1986-1995; 211684
  - Subseries A: Access Copies, cuid20961; 211685
  - Subseries B: Originals, 211686
    - A. Poets- Doug Messerli, 1986; ID: 173.0064; 211720 (Box 3, Media ID: 173.0064)
    - A. Bob & Bob Retro, 1986; ID: 173.006; 211721 (Box 3, Media ID: 173.006)
    - A. KFPK- Dark Bob, June 30, 1987; ID: 173.0066; 211722 (Box 3, Media ID: 173.0066)
    - A. John Malpede - LAPD, August 1986; ID: 173.0067; 211724 (Box 3, Media ID: 173.0067)
    - A. Rachel Rosenthal- Interview, September 1, 1987; ID: 173.0068; 211725 (Box 3, Media ID: 173.0068)
    - A Barry Yourgraw, December 8, 1987; ID: 173.0069; 211726 (Box 3, Media ID: 173.0069)
    - A. Remy Charlip/Steve Arnold/Car/Stone/Kedric Wolfe etc, February 16, 1988; ID: 173.0070; 211727 (Box 3, Media ID: 173.0070)
    - A. Irie!- British Dance Co., March 19. 1988; ID: 173.0071; 211729 (Box 3, Media ID: 173.0071)
    - A. Elisha Shapiro - Nihilist Party Political Convention, 1988; ID: 173.0072; 211730 (Box 3, Media ID: 173.0072)
      Orignal format: 1/4" audiocassette
    - A. LAPD (Los Angeles Poverty Dept Theater) - Frank, George, John, 1980s; ID: 173.0073; 211731 (Box 3, Media ID: 173.0073)
    - A. Belief - Elisha Shapiro, August 7, 1990; ID: 173.0074; 211736 (Box 3, Media ID: 173.0074)
    - A. Elisha Shapiro/Beth Lapides Live, 1992; ID: 173.0075; 211737 (Box 3, Media ID: 173.0075)
    - A. Terry Sweeney/Nancy Regan Performance, 1990's; ID: 173.0076; 211738 (Box 3, Media ID: 173.0076)
    - A. Spalding Gray Live, April 19, 1994; ID: 173.0077; 211739 (Box 3, Media ID: 173.0077)
    - A. Larry Miller & William de Ridder Live- Fluxus, August 23, 1994; ID: 173.0078; 211740 (Box 3, Media ID: 173.0078)
    - A. Women Vocalists (recorded), May 26, 1995; ID: 173.0079; 211741 (Box 3, Media ID: 173.0079)
- Series VII: Audio: Artists Tapes, 1990-1996; 211742
  - Subseries A: Access Copies, cuid20962; 211743
  - Subseries B: Originals, 211744
    - A. Anna Holmer & Geert Waegman - Blue Flame Blue, undated; ID: 173.0080; 211745 (Box 3, Media ID: 173.0080)
    - Untitled - Anna Holmer/Rod Poole, 1993; ID: 173.0081; 211746 (Box 3, Media ID: 173.0081)
    - A. Tim Rowe- Six Broken Lines - Rowe, Miano, Onserud, Miles, Kono, Siwula, 1996; ID: 173.0082; 211747 (Box 3, Media ID: 173.0082)
    - A. Audio Portraits - Tom Skelly, undated; ID: 173.0083; 211748 (Box 3, Media ID: 173.0083)
    - A. Port Menteau: Overlooking the Insignia B. X's Malingering/Forefinger Ajar - Sue Fishbein, undated; ID: 173.0084; 211749 (Box 3, Media ID: 173.0084)
    - A. Quiver - Dean Terry, 1994; ID: 173.0085; 211750 (Box 3, Media ID: 173.0085)
    - A. Curled Wire - Tim Boroian, 1990; ID: 173.0086; 211751 (Box 3, Media ID: 173.0086)
- Series VIII: Audio: Soundings Miscellaneous, 211753
  - Beat Town - Peter Beckman, undated; ID: 173.0087; 211752 (Box 4, Media ID: 173.0087)
    Original format: 1/4" Audio Reel Speed: 15 IPS Stereo
    General
    Live Mix-Master
- Series IX. Business Correspondence
  - A Space Toronto, 1979-1985; cuid20964 (Box 5)
  - Action/Image Journal, 1976-1985; cuid20965 (Box 5)
  - AGORA Foundation (Netherlands), 1979; cuid20966 (Box 5)
  - And/Or (Seattle), 1979; cuid20967 (Box 5)
  - Archive of Women in Architecture (Susana Torre), 1976; cuid20968 (Box 5)
  - Audio Arts (London), 1979-1982; cuid20969 (Box 5)
  - 80 Langston Street, San Francisco (Kathy O'Dell), 1978; cuid20970 (Box 5)
  - Experimental Art Foundation (Adelaide, Australia), 1977-1980; cuid20971 (Box 5)
  - Franklin Furnace (New York City), 1977; cuid20972 (Box 5)
  - Foundation for Today's Art/Bookworks (Philadelphia), 1982; cuid20973 (Box 5)
  - Independent Curators, Inc. (New York City), 1982-1985; cuid20974 (Box 5)
  - International Center for Photography (New York City), 1982; cuid20975 (Box 5)
  - The Kitchen (New York City), 1978; cuid20976 (Box 5)
  - LAAT (Los Angeles), 1984; cuid20977 (Box 5)
  - LACE (Los Angeles), 1980-1981; cuid20978 (Box 5)
  - LACPS (Los Angeles), 1985; cuid20979 (Box 5)
  - LAICA (Los Angeles), 1979-1980; cuid20980 (Box 5)
  - La Mamelle (San Francisco), 1978-1981; cuid20981 (Box 5)
  - N.A.M.E. Gallery/Landfall (Chicago), 1979-1981; cuid20982 (Box 5)
  - 112 Greene Street (New York City), 1977-1978; cuid20983 (Box 5)
  - On the Boards (Seattle), 1982-1983; cuid20984 (Box 5)
  - Performance Projects (Tuscon, Arizona), 1984; cuid20985 (Box 5)
  - Poets and Writers (New York City), 1979; cuid20986 (Box 5)
  - Portland Center for Visual Arts, 1978-1979; cuid20987 (Box 5)
  - Powerhouse Gallery and Cinema Parallelle (Montreal), 1979; cuid20988 (Box 5)
  - Printed Matter (New York City), 1976-1983; cuid20989 (Box 5)
  - P.S.1 (New York City), 1977; cuid20990 (Box 5)
  - Real Art Ways (Hartford, Connecticut), 1978-1981; cuid20991 (Box 5)
  - Riverside Studios (London), 1979-1980; cuid20992 (Box 5)
  - Soho Television, 1981; cuid20993 (Box 5)
  - South Hill Park Arts Centre (Bracknell, England), 1980-1981; cuid20994 (Box 5)
  - Time-Based Arts (Amsterdam, Netherlands), 1986; cuid20995 (Box 6)
  - Vanguard Gallery (Los Angeles), 1978-1979; cuid20996 (Box 6)
  - Washington Project for the Arts (Washington, D.C.), 1980-1982; cuid20997 (Box 6)
  - Women in Art: Working Papers, 1977; cuid20998 (Box 6)
  - The Womens Building (Los Angeles), 1978-1981; cuid20999 (Box 6)
  - Women and Their Work (Austin, Texas), 1981-1982; cuid21000 (Box 6)
  - Woodworks, Inc. (San Jose, California), 1978; cuid21001 (Box 6)
  - ZBS Foundation (New York), 1980-1983; cuid21002 (Box 6)
  - Contemporary Art Museum (Houston, Texas), 1977-1979; cuid21003 (Box 6)
  - C SPACE (New York City), 1977-1978; cuid21004 (Box 6)
  - Detroit Institute of the Arts (Mary Jane Jacob), 1979-1980; cuid21005 (Box 6)
  - Elise Meyer Gallery (New York City), 1980-1983; cuid21006 (Box 6)
  - ICA London, 1979-1986; cuid21007 (Box 6)
  - Long Beach Museum of Art (California), 1978-1990; cuid21008 (Box 6)
  - Laguna Gloria Museum of Art (Austin, Texas), 1981-1983; cuid21009 (Box 6)
  - Museo de Arte Contemporarana (Sao Paulo, Brazil), 1977-1978; cuid21010 (Box 6)
  - Museum of Modern Art (MoMA, New York City), 1978-1985; cuid21011 (Box 6)
  - Museum Moderna Kunst (Vienna), 1983-1985; cuid21012 (Box 6)
  - National Art Gallery (Wellington, New Zealand), 1978-1987; cuid21013 (Box 6)
  - National Gallery of Canada (Ottowa), 1979; cuid21014 (Box 6)
  - Poland Exhibition Invitations, 1979; cuid21015 (Box 6)
  - Queens Museum (New York City), 1981; cuid21016 (Box 6)
  - Richard De Marco Gallery (Edinburgh), 1976; cuid21017 (Box 6)
  - Rimini Museum (Italy), 1981-1982; cuid21018 (Box 6)
  - Robert Newman Gallery (Boulder, Colorado), 1979; cuid21019 (Box 6)
  - San Francisco Museum of Modern Art, 1980; cuid21020 (Box 6)
  - Stedelijk Museum (Amsterdam), 1979-1982; cuid21021 (Box 6)
  - University Art Museum, University of California-Berkeley, 1978; cuid21022 (Box 6)
  - Art Institute of Chicago, 1979-1980; cuid21023 (Box 6)
  - California Insitute of the Arts, 1979-1981; cuid21024 (Box 6)
  - Cal Arts, 1990s; cuid21025 (Box 6)
  - California State University, Chico (Gayle Kimball), 1978; cuid21026 (Box 6)
  - Cal Tech (Baxter Gallery), 1981; cuid21027 (Box 6)
  - Claremont Colleges (California), 1981-1982; cuid21028 (Box 6)
  - Concordia University (Montreal), 1979-1980; cuid21029 (Box 6)
  - Cranbrook and Wayne State University (Michigan), 1980-1981; cuid21030 (Box 6)
  - Kansas City Art Institute (Sherry Lacy), 1978; cuid21031 (Box 6)
  - Mass College of Art, 1978; cuid21032 (Box 6)
  - Melbourne University (Ewing and George Patton Gallery), 1977; cuid21033 (Box 6)
  - RE:PAGES Exhibition (Rhode Island), 1980-1981; cuid21034 (Box 6)
  - San Jose State University (California), 1978; cuid21035 (Box 6)
  - San Francisco Art Institute (Jim Pomeroy), 1978; cuid21036 (Box 6)
  - Texas Tour: Houseon, Rice University, NASA, G. Barnstone), 1980-1981; cuid21037 (Box 6)
  - U.S. Information Agency, 1976; cuid21038 (Box 6)
  - University of Arizona, Tucson, 1985; cuid21039 (Box 6)
  - University of California, Irvine, 1978-1980; cuid21040 (Box 6)
  - University of California, San Diego, 1978-1982; cuid21041 (Box 7)
  - University of California, Santa Barbara, 1978-1981; cuid21042 (Box 7)
  - University of Colorado (Lamia Dumato), 1978-1979; cuid21043 (Box 7)
  - University of Pennsylvania, Philadelphia ("Fresh Fish"), 1983; cuid21044 (Box 7)
  - University of Texas, Austin, 1977; cuid21045 (Box 7)